Everyone's dying to be them.
The Telling is a horror, thriller film directed by Nicholas Carpenter.
In this horror anthology film, three girls pledge the most
popular - and cruelest - sorority on campus.
For their final task, they must tell the scariest story they know.
Containing three distinct stories - one featuring a murderous doll, one a has-been actress and her
run in with a film crew of the undead and, finally, a hunt-and-kill fright-fest.
Eva DeMarco, played by Bridget Marquardt.
Stephanie, played by Holly Madison.
Brianna, played by Najarra Townsend.
Brianna's Mom, played by Angela Nicholas.
Haley, played by Jean Louise O'Sullivan.
Brandi (segment "Sorority Sisters"), played by Ashley Noel.
The Telling is a 2009 horror film starring Holly
Madison and Bridget Marquardt from the E!
television series The Girls Next Door.
The film is also the producing debut of Bridget Marquardt, who
teamed up with veteran producer Chuck Williams.
It is directed by Jeff Burr and first time director Nicholas
Carpenter, grandson of filmmaker Hal Roach.
The making of the film was featured on the popular
reality show The Girls Next Door.
The majority of the filming took place at the
Playboy Mansion and the Hollywood Castle.
In addition to Madison and Marquardt, Playboy Playmate of the Year
Sara Jean Underwood makes an appearance in the film.
The film explores themes of poison, undead, murder, sorority, pledge.
The tone is dark and intense.